If you take the traditional notion of
work and out of the purpose of what we
are, what's left?
>> AI is growing so fast, right? So, we
have no idea what next year would look
like or in 5 years, what would the job
market look like? What type of qualities
do companies need? So, how do we prepare
for a future world that we can't even
see?
>> There's some things that we can be
reasonably sure about. You and I grew up
with in a system that was designed to
shape us, sort us, channel us to
different kinds of careers where our
purpose in life was defined by what we
do principally. In a world where
knowledge is freely accessible, what you
look for is something that is scarce and
precious. What is it that we can do that
the machines can't?
>> Love, trust, die.
Such a privilege to have Tad with us. Oh
my god. I've been expecting you and
>> two hours. That's part of the problem.
>> And I have been studying your stuff. Oh
my god.
>> Just for two hours.
>> No, for days. Please don't tell me that.
>> Come on.
>> You are the professor at NYU Stern.
>> I am an adjunct professor at NYU Stern.
I have been for 25 years. 24, 25,
something like that.
>> You enjoy teaching?
>> Oh, I love it. I have over a thousand
former students, Bonnie. 1,000.
>> Wow. I have a question for you. AI is
growing so fast, right? So, we have no
idea what next year would look like or
in five years, what would the uh job
market look like? What type of qualities
do companies need? So, how do we prepare
for a future world that we can't even
see? Well, um there's some things that
we can be reasonably sure about.
>> Uh the first is that the rate of change
among both AI and robotics is parabolic
or if it isn't going to continue being
parabolic, it was going to have to slow
down very sharply. Mhm.
>> Second thing we can generally be sure of
is that for many many human tasks that
are conducted every day at the office
and the work uh the machine is already
better than we are.
>> Yeah.
>> Not perhaps so many general tasks mean
we're very flexible. We can shift around
but specific tasks much better. Um and
the third thing is unless we believe
there will be an disruption in the
parabolic growth that's going to be
accelerating in its truth and it's more
widespread in 5 years. Um so what we
have to look for is two things. One is
what is it that we can do that the
machines can't?
>> What what what can we do? Love
>> trust.
>> Trust. You're on a roll. Go for three
more.
>> Oh, empathy.
>> Empathy would be the third choice. Go.
You've got two more in you. I know that
you got this, Bonnie.
>> Wow. What can What can uh machines do?
>> Love, trust, empathy.
>> Give birth.
>> 100%. Birth. Yeah.
>> Die.
>> Can they die?
>> Um, well, you have to be alive in order
to die. So, you raise a very interesting
existential question.
Um but let's before we do give birth and
die um
how about
um provide judgment?
>> AI can do that.
>> Yes, but do you trust it?
>> Well, if it's a basic task, yes.
>> Right. But trust
>> trust is really interesting. I guess you
could trust your AI. You'll learn to
trust it. Um and um how about do
something inherently human?
>> Dance, play, experience joy.
>> Go out on a gorgeous day, walk up the
peak, whatever.
>> Do you need You don't need to learn
that.
>> Do you need to learn that though?
>> Well, it's experience being a human
>> human being.
>> Mhm.
>> And I don't think a machine can
experience being a human being.
Certainly the machines will tell you now
they don't experience being a human
being. Interestingly, we can't tell
whether they're right and they can't
tell whether they're wrong, but that's a
different story.
>> So, um, think about the possibility just
as a possibility and we're all
struggling with this because we don't
know what's coming, right? But think
about the possibility that
um you and I grew up
with in a system that was designed to
shape us, sort us and channel us to
different kinds of careers where our
purpose in life was defined by what we
do.
>> Yes.
>> Principally.
>> Now imagine that that is not the only
purpose for human beings. that in fact
for most of our history what we do was
actually a sideeshow to who we are and
how we experience life and the joy we
pass on and the experiences we have and
all those things and is it really
obviously there's going to be some
challenges and transition and also but
is it really impossible to believe that
if we strip away
Bitcoin from Bonnie
we have somebody that is even more human
than the one that is wired into the
powerful frame that you now exhibit.
>> I suspect yes is the answer.
>> But does it matter to other people?
>> Well, does it matter to you?
>> It matters to me. But
>> why
>> it takes because my identity is so much
bigger than just, you know, doing
podcast and my work, right? Um,
but you you don't have time to go around
and meet people and, you know, learn
about their hopes and dreams and fears,
but it's easier to learn their title and
what they do. It's just
>> Well, it's a shorthand.
>> Yeah. No, it's exactly what you said. We
we use the hi, what do you do
>> as a way of almost a way to put you on a
taxonomy of people.
>> We meet people every day. We look at
their resume. Whatever it is we do, we
do. We find them on LinkedIn, we check
them out on Twitter, check them out on
Instagram, whatever it is, Tik Tok. Um,
and you're right, we we put them in a
category.
And what I would pose to you
is that you actually touched on the most
important question that we're all going
to face with the advent of the machine,
which is if you take the traditional
notion of work and out of the purpose of
what we are,
what's left?
>> Oh,
>> and moreover, how do we respond to
what's left?
>> That is scary.
>> That's what you just said.
>> Yeah, I know. And it's really powerful
stuff because when you when we look into
the future, we can be incredibly
optimistic, but we can't be presumably
optimistic without some tinge of anxiety
if we're honest with ourselves.
>> And the reason in my opinion is because
of what you just said, which is, wow, if
you take the Bitcoin out of Bitcoin
Bonnie, I have to think about what my
identity means in a completely new way.
And I worked so hard to get to this
identity. And this identity is clear and
understand how it fits in the context of
what we're all doing. And now I have to
think about a completely new one. And
it's only because a machine came along
and did my podcast better than I did.
>> Mhm. I actually watched this interview
um long time ago and they're like, I
challenge you to go on a date with
somebody without telling them what you
do. Like you just you you cannot talk
about your job.
So who are you? What do you do? What do
you like? What is your dream? It is very
hard.
>> It's very hard, but it is possible. The
question is whether it's worth doing.
>> Is it? I mean, do you want to be with a
partner
that fundamentally is committed to doing
something that in which you have no
interest?
>> You know what? I'm actually not smart
enough to answer this question. This is
deep.
>> Well, you started. I'm just following
your interview rules. I This is your
show.
>> Wow. But okay, let's say you're teaching
all these students.
>> I'm teaching them about art and AI.
>> Right.
>> What do you want them to take away if
there if you again?
>> Three things.
>> Okay. Number one, I want them to use AI
in the classroom, out of the classroom,
and I uh want them to show that they're
using AI, and I want them to use it in
preparation and on the fly. I want them
to talk about their prompts. I want them
to show us how they're using the
prompts, how they're thinking about it.
I want I want all of it disclo I want it
out in the open. I don't want to be
using blue books or any of the thing.
Going back to handwriting, all that
nonsense. I don't want any of that. I
want them to use AI like it's their
partner, like it's their coach.
Number two,
I want them to get comfortable
>> not learning by spending all their time
digging into books, chasing down facts.
We're talking about a class where
suddenly you've got access to all the
knowledge in the world and can write
things instantly and can answer
questions instantly. So this goes
profoundly to what is the role of the
student
>> because that's what we spend our time on
in in education right and the third
thing is I want to create an opportunity
for and this is particularly important
with respect to what we're doing which
is art and the intersection of human
creativity and the machine. Um I want
them to think about all the things that
you and I just began to think about
right there which is how do our values
change? How does creativity change? What
does it mean to be human? What does it
mean to be an educated person in a world
where knowledge is ubiquitous and
essentially free?
>> Mhm.
>> And that is a big profound question. If
they come out of that plus a little bit
of understanding about how technology
affects art, I will declare victory.
I asked people this question a while
ago, but nobody could really answer me
this question, which is let's say
everybody is now using AI. We have a
whole generation of people. I'm talking
to you. I'm not sure what to ask you.
So, I'm just going to ask AI. What
should I ask?
>> And you don't know how to answer my
question. So, you ask AI, how should I
answer Bonnie's last question? Mhm.
>> Now,
I'm not sure if this pause is,
you know, polite. So, I ask AI, is it is
it okay in Tad's um culture that I pause
when I talk to him? Who am I now? Now,
I'm being controlled by AI. Everything I
do, all the responses
um is formed by AI. Now, I am being
controlled.
So you have a whole generation of kids
just being trained by AI.
>> So
>> is that weird? That's
>> okay. That's the question. Is that
weird?
>> I don't know. So
>> yes, it's totally discontinuous from our
experience.
>> Right. But how do you
>> By the way, we have a whole lot of kids
plugged into their phones now.
>> But they are not asking their phone what
they should do or what they should eat.
>> Correct. Correct. Correct. you're on
another important path which is a very
dystopic possibility about the future
could be that we you know we were
talking humorously when when I came in a
few minutes ago about the red pill blue
pill
>> the blue pill begins to look pretty good
>> explain that
>> remember the red pill it takes you off
the matrix and you see the way things
really are and the blue pill you happily
go about your day and you have no idea
that you're actually plugged into the
matrix right
>> what you're describing is a situation
where it might just be easier not to
have to deal with what does it mean that
I have to be independent and I have to
create a purpose for myself that's
independent and moreover I have to be
the agent in what I say and do rather
than just be told what I'm going to be
doing by AI. My worry is that our
humanity
becomes a little bit less powerful
because of the reason you said which is
we just wait around being told what to
do. We can't get to that place.
>> But we are going to get there.
>> Well, no one really is sure, but I would
agree with you. It is a risk.
>> And how does Bitcoin fit in this new AI
era? Well, um, in a world where
knowledge is free,
>> okay, think about think about how many
things we invest in where what we're
really investing in is superior
knowledge or superior capability or
superior IP or any of those things. But
in a world where knowledge is freely
accessible,
um, what you look for is something that
is scarce and precious.
>> And, uh, this is not financial advice.
We always like to say that and it isn't.
But in my way of thinking, Bitcoin is
both scarce and precious and a
spectacular store of value. So if you
don't know where to put your money,
I can't say where to put your money, but
I'll tell you one thing. I would default
to Bitcoin.
>> Mhm. You are the former CEO of South and
um Madison Square Garden.
>> Both. Yes.
>> Insane.
>> Or each. Yes.
This is like this is what I was talking
about the perfect resume which is the uh
you're the kid that all parents want
their kids to be.
>> That's interesting. Some parents might
>> you know parents have different
aspirations for their kids.
>> Okay. Well, you have a very good path.
>> I have a very traditional path.
Princeton, Harvard,
>> um lots of corporate jobs.
>> Yeah. Uh yeah, sure. And then
>> life was good.
>> My life I've been blessed. My life's
very good.
>> But then
you start realizing that the money
system is broken.
>> Um yes.
>> How? Because if I am enjoying my life
and I would like the situation to remain
this way, I would not question the
system.
>> Well, the the way you frame the
question, there are lots of pieces to
it. Let me start with the first question
you asked which is when was the
realization
>> that something was unusual going on
>> and what why did it why did it affect
me? So the original realization was when
I
began to start listening to
uh Raul Powell and Michael Sailor and
Dan Tapiro, three people you're probably
familiar with, um who were talking about
something a little bit unusual to me,
which was the effect of actual monetary
debasement on investment portfolios.
Mhm.
>> And um and it became clear to me that uh
I had been thinking about wealth
creation
um in ways that were not fully cognizant
of the way the devaluation of money not
versus other currencies
>> versus goods and services and crucially
assets. Of course it was obvious to me
that certain kinds of assets grow faster
than the inflation rate. But the um I
mean you know I houses, art, all sorts
of things, gold, all these things. Um
but what what hadn't really occurred to
me was the effect of debasement in terms
of creating value for versus say the
stock market.
And when it became clear to me that I
had been viewing things not quite right,
meaning I understood finance and I could
do all sorts of fascinating things with
finance,
>> but that the foundation of money I had
not built into the premise that it was
constantly inevitably by government
policy devaluing versus goods, services,
and assets in particular. The moment I
hit that bang, I'm like, "Wait,
my entire theory of investing, my
investing strategy is wrong. It's just
wrong."
>> And um and maybe the way I think about
value is wrong.
>> Um and so that's how I did it. But but
remember that that's the way somebody
who has things to invest comes to it.
That's not the way somebody who is
trying to figure out how to buy a house
or how they'll ever buy a house or how
they'll pay for groceries. So, in the
sense that you pointed out, yes, I I was
lucky enough and blessed enough not to
have those problems, but it still came
to me. Admittedly, it's much much more
difficult for very very successful
people to see Bitcoin
>> really
>> in my opinion than it is for people who
aren't. And and the reason is because
what you said, which is the fiat system
largely works for them. And so what you
what they have to do is they have to be
thinking about innovative ways to expand
their investment horizons.
very rich people can actually borrow
money very cheaply almost free to buy
more Bitcoin. Are we just replaying the
old financial system the injustice?
>> Well, um very wealthy people can borrow
but it's not free
>> almost free.
>> Uh it's not even almost free. It is
there the rates are high right now. Um
but but what you do want to say is it's
freely available.
>> That's the difference. That's meaning
that the big difference between people
that have a whole lot of money and
people that don't have a lot of money
>> is the banks want to lend to the ones
who have a whole lot of money. It's the
availability of credit, but the price of
credit right now is still expensive.
>> Mhm.
>> Does it change your answer? I don't
know. I don't know. Doesn't change your
question. So to the second part of your
question, listen, in so far as Bitcoin
has a purpose that is designed to make
it possible for everyone to achieve a
certain financial liberation.
There is no question that the more
concentrated the holdings of Bitcoin,
the more
in trouble that goal is.
Let's say something is really really
expensive. The price tag says it's $10
million. You naturally put more value on
it for some reason. Let's say we have
>> a debent good things that are more
expensive you value more highly.
>> Yes.
>> Why? Why is that? And
>> very profound question.
>> Yeah.
>> So um of course art
>> has this quality.
>> Yeah. Um, and that's because we are
social creatures.
>> And moreover, not only are we social
creatures, we like to establish
our position
visav our other friends and colleagues
and species, frankly, and um in all
sorts of different ways. And one of the
ways is to show people new and
innovative things. Another way, by the
way, is to wear your hair differently or
wear different clothes or do something
interesting or do something flashy or be
a podcaster. I mean, there are lots of
ways to do it and have lots of
followers.
>> Um, but one way also is to buy things
that are unattainable
>> in a way to signal that you've attained
something. And by the way, even if you
don't show them, sometimes it's gives
you a private sense of satisfaction that
you did. It's like an achievement. And
that's comes from the fact we are
inherently a social and mimetically
driven species.
And that's not going away. Okay. So,
let's make a slightly more complicated
example. Um, you've got a piece that's
worth 10 million
>> and it can be either $10 million at the
price level or $200.
>> Mhm.
>> Now, suppose a piece in this room of 20
people and they can all afford 10
million.
Suppose you then insert a piece of
information into that room that tells
you the thing's worth $5.
And then suppose you send another piece
of information that says, "No, no, we
made a mistake. We meant $50 million."
The point is how we think about price is
in reference to what we think the value
is. And in situations where you have a
painting that you neither like nor you
you not you don't dislike and you don't
like. You're sort of neutral on the
painting. Um
you're fundamentally going to have to
look for reference points that will give
you an anchor to think about what the
price is in relation to because the last
thing you want to do is spend $10
million for something that isn't worth
$200 isn't worth $200. So we inherently
look for pricing reference points and
Bitcoin is all about that.
>> Tell me more.
>> Well um uh if you look at a house for
example
>> if you go back 8 to 10 years a house
priced in Bitcoin was quite a lot of
Bitcoin
like in the hundreds of Bitcoin. Like
close to 700 Bitcoin eight years ago.
Today it's five.
>> Yeah.
>> For the median house price at least in
the United States.
That says, and yet at the same time, we
perceive houses to be more expensive
than ever in dollar terms.
Meaning, isn't the whole sort of meme, I
don't know if it's true in Hong Kong,
but it's true in the United States, the
whole meme is nobody can afford a house.
And yet, in Bitcoin terms, it's become
so affordable it's almost ridiculous.
So, think about the reference point of
Bitcoin as the unit of as the standard
measure of value there. And what you see
is that Bitcoin has changed. Anyone who
owned Bitcoin over that period of time
has found housing very very inexpensive.
>> Very, very inexpensive. If you didn't,
you found housing to be incredibly
expensive. All of that is a reference
point.
>> In the one case, Bitcoin's a reference
point. In the other, the US dollar is.
>> So, we used to use US dollar. Now,
>> we use it now, by the way. You use Hong
Kong dollars and Taiwan dollar. Yeah.
Exactly.
But are you seeing a world that would
change to the Bitcoin standard
or are we still the minority?
>> Well, there are two things to let me
split the question in two pieces. One is
do I see the dollar's role as a a a
mechanism of currency exchange and and
transmission going away in the near
term? No. Do I see people thinking about
what
goods and services and assets in
particular around them
are going to be versus Bitcoin as a
store of value? Yes, I do see that
accelerating. I think that is a really
powerful tool because if you began,
Bonnie, to think about your entire life
as if I'm going to spend X dollars on
this, I have to sell Bitcoin to do it
because otherwise I would take those
dollars and buy Bitcoin.
>> That means everything to you
conceptually is priced in Bitcoin. And
let me tell you something.
If you start pricing everything in
Bitcoin and you wanna get more and more
Bitcoin, you're going to be buying a lot
less of other stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> There's a whole lot of things you're
going to want to buy that that you used
to buy that you don't want to buy
anymore if you think about every single
one of those things is going into
Bitcoin.
>> How do I enjoy my life if that is the
case? Like if my ultimate life goal is
to just accumulate as many Bitcoin as I
can, but I only have one life. Well, I
would urge you, not that you've asked
for advice, this is not financial
advice. This is just advice
that
someone as obviously talented and
charismatic as you can come up with a
more exciting life purpose than just
accumulating as much Bitcoin as
possible. Bitcoin is an enabling thing
to something else. So the question for
you is, how do you make that something
else really special?
>> That's someone older speaking to someone
on her way up in a blinding flash of
glory.
>> Thank you. If you um give your kids
advice, would you say well your your
earlier point was
pretty much all in Bitcoin then? like
except for your
>> I have a lot of things other than
Bitcoin,
>> but I made a choice to do that.
>> Now, interestingly, I did sell my wine
collection and convert it into Bitcoin.
>> Um, and the reason I did is because I I
I'm not drinking very much. It's, you
know, I I love wine. I love French
Burgundies in particular. I mean, I love
French Burgundies, but I'm just not
drinking less because I'm more focused
on health and um and it's not a good
store of value compared to Bitcoin. It's
a beautiful store of value, but I mean,
I great, but Bitcoin's better, so I
bought Bitcoin. So the question would be
if Bitcoin is such a superior asset, why
don't you sell everything else and just
buy this
>> because then I would have nothing else.
>> That's the balance, right? Well,
>> enjoy life. Do you want to own other
things?
>> Yeah, but Bitcoin is Bitcoin is not the
end
>> of
the end purpose of my life.
>> Um it is an enabling purpose. It is a
way to outrun the money printer. It's a
way to force yourself to save and
invest. It's a way to provide you with
um opportunities to give your kids
opportunities. Um it's a uh philosophy
of independence.
Um it is all these different things. um
and um self-actualization, if you will
take that job, that that word too. Those
are all the things. But notice that life
purpose isn't on the list.
>> Bitcoin is not it may be, by the way,
let's do Michael Sailor as an example.
Michael Sailor may have his life purpose
to spread the gospel of Bitcoin and
empower many millions of other people.
And I think he's been doing that. Um
that's a life purpose. I get that. Um,
but for me to accumulate as much Bitcoin
as possible, interestingly, I don't even
think that's his life purpose. I I I
don't I I I don't know. I've never asked
him, but but I think his life purpose is
to spread the gospel of Bitcoin and and
try to help more people solve big
problems both in their lives and more
generally by having more Bitcoin. And
Strategy, the company, is a means to
that. And it's interesting because um he
has stated publicly he wants to give it
all away when he passes away. He wants
you know give it all away and uh or or
put it all in you know put it all in a
foundation or something like that. And
my perspective on it is that tells you
his life even his life purpose is bigger
than Bitcoin.
>> Mhm.
>> Meaning it's not Bitcoin it's Bitcoin to
an end and the end is a higher purpose.
It's a human purpose.
>> What could the higher purpose be?
teaching people how the financial
education we were taught is broken.
>> Well, you do that now.
>> Yes, I do that.
>> And that is a higher purpose. And by the
way, it's a noble and important purpose.
>> It's crazy how Bitcoin changes
>> how I view money.
>> Good.
>> And it's also crazy how
many people out there don't know about
this.
>> That's exactly why your purpose is
important.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> but that's a really important that's my
point. You you have a purpose that's
bigger than Bitcoin. Bitcoin is an
input, an operational input to your
purpose. Your purpose is to provide
honestly financial
pathways to freedom and to realization
of bigger goals to all the people who at
the moment don't see that.
>> Can you summarize what is the biggest
problem to our financial education
nowadays in Asia? It could be, hey,
save, save up and buy a house because
that is a symbol of being successful,
right? And if you don't have a house,
you're not really supposed to get
married. You're not supposed to you're
not considered an adult. I I can't make
a broad sweeping statement, but I'll
I'll make one that applies to me,
>> which is
um you can learn finance without
learning how to deal with or manage
money.
>> Okay,
but that's like I'm learning something I
have never had.
>> Finance and how to manage money are
different. H it's one is more like
banking
>> one is well banking financing companies
doing all those things it's very
numerical and has to do with money and
it has to do with finance
>> but that's different from managing your
money
>> okay tell me that
>> managing your money is how you really
manage yourself
>> in a world of scarce resources
that's a completely different question
and by the way it's true that those
resources are measured in money. So,
we're talking about how you manage
money, but how to manage money is how
you manage yourself. For example, do you
spend more than you bring in?
>> Mhm.
>> Do you work hard, earn more than you
bring in, and then you put it in
instruments that either lose money or
lose traction against the broader market
or frankly don't make any sense? Um, do
you provide for the people that are
relying upon you to provide for them?
Those are how you manage money. That's
very different.
>> So, most people,
>> not most people,
>> most people know how to manage money or
>> I don't know whether most people know
how to manage money or not. But I'll
tell you one thing. I can tell you that
it's there are a lot of people in the
world who do not know how to manage
money.
>> Of course.
>> Yeah.
>> But most people also do not understand
finance.
Well, so aspects of finance, capital
asset pricing model.
>> Yeah, but that's it.
>> Well, no, there are other things. Black
Scholes theorem, the um there are
portfolio arbitrage theory, you know,
the sharp ratio. You there are a long
list of things that are highly technical
finance terms
>> that are very useful in the modern
financial world
>> that are different from managing money.
Understanding how Bitcoin fits into your
life is a question of how you manage
your life in a world of scarce
resources. And that's a question of how
you manage your life's money, your own
money.
>> How would you define money?
>> Money for me is either a store of value,
a medium of exchange, or a unit of
account.
That's pretty basic stuff.
>> Is it also a way to store your time and
energy?
>> Yes.
When I work hard, I invest time.
>> Yeah.
>> And I get money in return. The money
allows me to buy other things or to do
other things or do whatever I want or by
the way invest in more money to create
more money. But that is a way to have
converted my energy, my work
into
um a storage unit money that I can then
redeploy to something else. Yes. So
money is an encapsulation of my time and
my effort, my time and my energy
deployed. Oh, and by the way, often my
intelligence, right? And I don't mean
intelligence IQ. I mean just actual
thinking work.
>> Imagine this world. There's no fiat
system. Okay? There's only Bitcoin. And
let's say Bitcoin money is a store of
human energy, time, effort, intelligent,
everything that we just mentioned.
How does that world world look like?
Because everybody is fighting over a
limited resource.
Unlike fiat, there's no limit to it,
right? You just feel like you have
abundant of fiat money being printed.
So, you don't really have to fight over
something. It's not that $1 I earn is
not from you. But in this world where
money is kept,
the one Bitcoin I own is supposedly
taken from you. Or if I own this one,
then there is no way you can own the
same one. How does that world look like?
Are we going to be
more competitive?
Is this world going to be a little more
evil?
>> Well, I you'd be pleased to hear I'm
much more optimistic than that. Um, uh,
it's true that they're only 21 million
Bitcoin.
>> Mhm.
>> But each of those has literally millions
and millions of Satoshi's,
>> right? And you can imagine that the
difference between the fiat world and
what you're describing as a Bitcoin
standard, Bitcoin standard world, is not
that money is limited.
>> Mhm.
>> I'll come to that in a minute. I know
you're questioning that. It's instead
that money appreciates in value versus
everything else, not depreciates.
So for example, suppose we didn't focus
on Bitcoin. We focused on Satoshi's.
>> Okay?
>> Satoshi's right now are very very
inexpensive versus the dollar. Very very
inexpensive.
>> Um and over time they're going to get
more and more and more and more and more
expensive versus the dollar. Yeah. So
until that until we can no longer until
it becomes a you know um one Satoshi
equals a cup of coffee there's plenty of
subsets of the Bitcoin standard to use
for currency. You see that? Mhm.
>> And by the way, if at some point in the
far future where Satoshi's we don't have
enough of them, well, let's do I don't
know Desa Satoshi's or Centa Satoshi's
where we break them into another hundred
because each of them is increasing in
value. And and so the way to think about
it is the big difference between the
fiat world and the Bitcoin world is that
money gets more valuable in the Bitcoin
world and money gets less valuable in
the fiat world. I love this conversation
because it's not only about Bitcoin and
finance and money. It's also about life.
>> Well, that's the point of what you're
doing.
>> As far as I can see, your point is to
help people have better lives with
Bitcoin as an operational element to
that. And guess what? That's a good
purpose. And so, back to the question
you asked me originally, what are we
going to do? Well, as human beings,
having a purpose is inherently human.
And by the way, the machines don't have
one except what we give them. Second
point, choosing to help others.
While it is true machines can help
others, it's not obvious they can choose
to help others independent of us. We
have to tell them to choose to help
others. And then finally, you can enjoy
helping others. And maybe the machines
can do that. Maybe they can fool us into
thinking they can, but unless we somehow
figure out a way for them to do it or
they figure out a way for them to do it,
only human beings can do that. And so
the three basic elements of what you're
trying to do will still be here.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Pleasure. Thank you for having me. I
love Hong Kong. Every time I come, I
say, "Oh my gosh, greatest city in the
world. Thank you for hosting me here."
>> Thank you. Thank you.